Shuichi Iguchi!
It is the League of Villains!
Damn it!
--That's hard!
--I'm going closer!
Deadbolt!
Sorry!
Dabi!
Whoopsie-daisy.
You're too persistent!
Bastards... What are you up to--
Don't ask pointless questions.
Why are the heroes here?
The information was leaked...
Leaked? From where...?
Who knows...
They got past the pursuit team. Now--
You don't have to spell it out.
Leave it to me.
Endeavor!
The one who's moved up to number one, huh?
It's so late.
You're working hard!
Jetburn!
Hey, hey, hey!
I'll run you over, Endeavor!
Mister, get back.
Prominence Burn!
Damn it, is this it?
Endeavor...
You were here?
Why didn't you give us a hand, Hawks?
I just got here, Endeavor.
What about the League guys?
They were all doubles
made with Twice's Quirk.
What's this?
A life-support system...?
To transport a new type of Nomu or something?
What did you say?!
What in the world are Shigaraki
and the others transporting...?
I was getting tired of waiting, Nine.
It was worth the wait.
The experiment was a success.
The world has become a superhuman society,
and about 80% of the world's population
now has some kind of special trait.
"Superhuman Society" and about 80% of the world's
population now has some kind of special trait.
"Superhuman Society"
I, Izuku Midoriya, was Quirkless,
but then I had a fateful meeting with All Might,
and he transferred the Quirk,
One For All, to me.
"U.A. High School"
And then, I enrolled in the
hero course at U.A. High School,
the prestigious school
that has produced many heroes...
I continue to run toward my dream.
That's right,
this is the story of how
I became the greatest hero.
Hey, girls! Come hang out with us!
--Yeah, yeah!
--No, thanks.
Don't say tha--
--What the heck?!
--I-It won't come off!
Are you hurt?
Ladies.
--Thanks!
--You saved us!
No, that wasn't me just now...
Down! Look down!
Asui, 70 meters past the rocks!
There's a child drowning!
Mommy! Momm--
A-Are you okay?
Why are you crying?
He's scared of your face, huh?
Swimming prohibited! Swimming prohibited!
Swimming prohibited past the rocks!
"Off Limits"
"Off Limits" It's dangerous to go
past here, so please don't enter!
It's dangerous to go past here,
so please don't enter!
--That's amazing!
--Not bad!
It's not a show...
Shoto, can you make me more ice?
Sure.
"Shaved Ice"
"Shaved Ice" --Here you go.
--That's too big!
--Here you go.
There are so many heroes!
Oh?
Mahoro?
U.A. Hero Agency.
Okay, I'll send someone right away.
Kaminari, Mr. Matsuda in the west district
said his battery's gone bad again.
Again?
That old man needs to get a new one!
Do your best, Chargebolt!
--Go, go!
Hi, this is U.A. Hero Agency.
We'll solve anything for you with a sparkle.
You found the lost dog?
Yeah, just now.
Don't worry, the dog's fine.
Good work. Next, you'll be looking for a parrot.
My little brother's lost.
I can't find him anywhere!
It's okay, calm down.
--First, what are you and your brother's names?
--Don't worry... Of course!
Iida, Granny Sato threw out her back!
Got it.
I will rush over at once!
There's a lost child in the shopping arcade!
Any heroes who are free right now--
--No way.
--That was fast!
Don't say that, Bakugo!
Uraraka, I'll go with you--
"Nabu Island Guidebook"
You can't find a lost kid with your Quirk!
If we're looking for lost kids...
...then it's my turn.
Uraraka, I'll go, too.
"Iogi Heights"
"U.A. High School 1-A Agency"
One For All: Full Cowling... 8%!
Hero Agency!
Class 1-A!
Heading out!
The 20 of us in U.A. High School's
hero course Class 1-A...
...have come to Nabu Island,
an island far from the main island of Japan.
Even though we've acquired
our provisional hero licenses,
why are we students working
as heroes on this island?
"Last Month - U.A. High School"
why are we students working
as heroes on this island?
"Last Month - U.A. High School"
Of course, there is a reason behind it...
"Principal's Office"
Placing hero course students
in areas with no pro heroes...
A practical hero work recommendation project?
Yes, the current superhuman society
is in the midst of chaos.
You, the number one hero and Symbol of Peace,
are effectively retired.
The villains are gaining power because of that.
Are you saying that in order
to go up against them,
it is imperative that we train
the next generation of heroes?
The top brass at the Heroes
Public Safety Commission think so.
Well, I'm sure you have
your thoughts about this,
but I hope you will cooperate with us.
The hero work recommendation project.
"Nabu Island"
"Nabu Island" You all will be stationed on Nabu
Island, an outlying island in southern Japan.
"Nabu Island"
Their hero-in-residence retired due to old age.
"Nabu island" You all will work as
heroes there until a successor arrives.
You all will work as heroes there
until a successor arrives.
That's super hero-like!
I mean, we will be heroes!
Excited, yay!
I'm bursting with eagerness!
This isn't an internship or a work study.
It's real hero work...
I've wanted to be a hero since I was little...
Finally, I will...
Listen to what I have to say until the end.
All right.
As a rule, you will have no backup
from teachers or pro heroes.
Of course, if anything happens,
you all will bear the responsibility for it.
Bear that in mind and behave as a hero should.
Understand?
Yes, sir!
"Nabu Island Fishing Association"
Mahoro, where are you?
--Where are you, Maho--
--Katsuma?
You're Katsuma Shimano, right?
A hero...
You got separated from your big sister, right?
Now, come with me--
You're late! That took too long!
--Mahoro...
--What's your name?
D-Deku...
Um, who are you?
Katsuma's big sister, Mahoro!
Huh? Then you found your little brother already?
That's great.
That's not great at all!
"Stopwatch"
Why did it take over an hour
to find a lost kid? Explain yourself!
"Stopwatch"
You're part of that famous
U.A.'s hero course, but you're useless.
If this is what we get, then maybe that
grandpa hero we had before'd be better!
I-I'm sorry...
Well, I guess it can't be helped,
since you're still a high schooler.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Deku?
Next time, make sure you do
your hero job properly, okay, Deku?
R-Right, I'll be more careful next time...
Let's go, Katsuma.
O-Okay...
U-Um...
Thanks...
You don't have to thank him!
Deku, what's going on?
What are you apologizing for?
I got scolded for taking
too long finding a lost kid.
Huh? What the heck?
But I'm glad...
About what?
That Katsuma was able
to get back to his sister safely.
Deku, you really feel like Deku, huh?
Huh? What do you mean?
That you're a hero through and through!
"Nabu Corner Store" "Restrooms"
Those heroes were useless, like I thought.
It's not like a small island like this
has any crime in the first place.
I'm sure they're probably especially bad,
even for U.A. students.
They came to look for me, though.
That boy was definitely a hero.
Hmph. Then I'll be the one
to unmask who he really is!
Mahoro?!
"At the same time"
I wonder if the Class A students
are being proper heroes...
The population of Nabu Island is 1,000.
In the last 30 years,
they've only had trivial crimes.
Anyway, I'm sure they'll be fine.
Besides, being a hero doesn't just
mean facing huge disasters by yourself
or fighting evil villains like what you did.
Interacting with those they protect will
also be an important experience for them.
I'm exhausted...
We've gone Plus Ultra beyond what's
allowed by the Labor Standards Act.
Class Reps, don't you think
we've taken on too many small jobs?
We shouldn't treat small
and large jobs differently.
Even if we're working as heroes,
we're still students.
We must do them faithfully and
earn the trust of the people of the island.
Excuse me! There's someone here who
hasn't done any hero work since we got here.
I've been staying in the office on purpose!
What're you gonna do if a villain
comes out while you jerks are out, huh?!
There aren't any villains on this island.
Excuse us.
Mr. Mayor!
Thanks for carrying Granny
to the hospital earlier.
Thanks for fixing my bike.
And our battery!
And for keeping the beach safe!
Here's some fresh fish!
It's not meant to replace our gratitude,
but please eat it if you'd like.
Let's eat!
You people! Show some restraint!
Thank you for going to all this trouble.
Oh no, it's really been
a big help having you all here.
We're counting on you from now on, too.
--Of course!
--We will do our very best to carry out our duty!
Thanks for the food!
That was delicious!
I can feel the kindness of people in my body.
It's moments like these
that make me glad I became a hero.
Yeah.
Kacchan of the Bakugos!
We're gonna take baths and go to sleep.
So we're counting on you for the night watch!
Why?!
Because you didn't do anything all day.
1,365... 1,366...
--1,367... 1,368...
--I will tell you the truth.
My Quirk is the power to transfer power...
One For All!
One person cultivates the power
and passes it on to another person,
who also cultivates it and passes it on.
It is the crystallization of power that spins
together the voices of those who need help
and the hearts of the brave.
And next, it is your turn.
Now that you have inherited One For All,
you may one day have
to fight against this great evil...
Next, it's your turn.
Right now, I can only use
One For All at 20% at the most.
I need to work harder and harder
so I can make this Quirk my own.
Kacchan!
--Oh, thanks for going on patrol.
--Looks like you've grown a bit with your One For All.
We can't talk about that here...!
I'm impatient.
I-I know that better than anybody.
I've known you since we were kids.
Then hurry up and make your Quirk your own
and fight me!
I'll prove to you
that I'm the one who will become number one.
Yeah, I'll definitely make
my Quirk my own and show you.
In order to become the greatest hero...
And I'll be better than the greatest.
Um...
You're from this afternoon...
A-A villain's...
...come out!
A villain?!
Tell me more!
"Heroes Public Safety Commission"
There have been continuous acts of
violence against heroes since last week.
All the victims were knocked unconscious...
...and they all lost their Quirks.
Shigaraki and his group have acquired
a Quirk-erasing needle manufactured illegally
by a designated villain group.
Do we have reports of them
succeeding in their mass production?
No, we do not.
Then investigate.
Continue your secret inves--
Have you thought about the possibility
that their Quirks were stolen?
What?
The victims were heroes,
so the Quirks that were lost
were naturally all useful ones.
If the suspect has a Quirk
that can steal Quirks like All For One...
That's...
Well, either way, it's related to Shigaraki.
I'll try investigating both possibilities.
So, where'd the cargo end up?
The heroes didn't collect it, right?
Yeah, that's been confirmed.
What was the cargo, anyway?
According to Doctor,
there's no need for us to know.
What the hell?
He just makes us do the transporting,
but he won't tell us anything?
Doesn't it make you even more curious?
Anyway, forget about it. Got it?
Roger!
No way!
Tomura Shigaraki.
Do not touch that.
Forget about it.
Doctor...
"Kyushu Region"
You said the next time you could
come home was in ten days, right?
Daddy, do your best at work.
You don't have to worry about us!
I'll take good care of Katsuma.
Thanks, Mahoro, Katsuma.
I'll bring back as many souvenirs as--
I've finally found it...
F-Found what...?
Don't worry, I won't kill you.
But I'll take your Quirk.
We finally got it, huh?
With this, we can make it a reality...
The new world...
...that we desire.
Nine?!
Wh-Why?
Why...?
It doesn't work on type B blood...
What?
After coming this far,
we're back to square one? Damn it!
No, there's still a way.
Daddy, do your best at work.
--You don't have to worry about us!
--I see...
Quirks...
...are hereditary...
Why are you here, too, damn Deku?!
Why? Because if there really is a villain--
I'll be fine by myself!
Hey, where'd you see the villain?!
I-Inside those castle ruins!
Tell me that first!
Mahoro...!
Over there!
Go hide.
Katsuma!
Stun Grenade!
This guy's...
Kacchan!
Huh?
Ouch!
The villain...
Ow, ow... Jeez!
At least get a little scared!
Th-That girl...
You're the one who made that villain illusion?
Gulp
"gulp"
Huh? How did you know it was an illusion?
It's obvious!
There's no shadow!
Hey, damn kid,
are you having fun taunting heroes?! Well?!
I'm completely different
from your everyday heroes.
I'm the one who'll be better than
All Might and take the number one spot,
Katsuki Bakugo!
"angry" "angry" "angry"
You picked the wrong person to taunt!
D-Don't scold my big sister.
"angry" "angry" "angry"
Huh?!
Are you her accomplice? Then--
You're going overboard, Kacchan!
Let go, damn Deku!
We should just be glad
it was kids playing tricks.
--Katsuma!
--That's the kind of attitude that
makes kids these days act impudent!
--Wait, damn it!
--I told you to stop!
--Don't give me orders!
Wh-What's up with that Bakugo guy anyway?
Become the number one hero?
Isn't he confusing it with the
ranking of heroes who look like villains?
He... came to save us.
Katsuma, do you want to be a hero that badly?
I'm against it. It's dangerous.
Besides, I know of someone
even cooler than a hero.
Who?
Daddy.
He's always thinking of us and protecting us.
I want you to be as cool as that.
Among the victims, there's
another one who's lost his Quirk.
But this time, he isn't a hero...
On top of that, everything that can be
used to identify him has been stolen.
The suspect doesn't want anyone
to know what Quirk he stole...?
Why does he need to hide it?
Hello, this is the U.A. Hero Agency.
Your travel bag has gone missing?
Okay, we'll send someone right away.
At the shopping arcade,
a tourist said she lost her luggage--
I'll go, I'll go!
Aoyama, come with me!
Oui.
Another lost item?
People should at least try to--
The client sounded really cute on the phone.
I can't leave someone in trouble alone!
Shoji is asking for more support on the beach.
Then, I'll go.
I will go on a regular patrol.
I'll go out, too, to help
with the fields at the Nijimas.
I'm off!
Katsuma...?
Is something the matter?
U-Um...
S-Sorry about yesterday...
You're so well-mannered!
You came to apologize?
It's okay, I'm not mad.
Will you tell the other hero I'm sorry, too?
Sure, I'll tell him.
But Katsuma, why did you do that yesterday?
My big sister hates heroes.
Yesterday, too, she said that
even if I said there were villains,
the heroes would be scared
and wouldn't come save me,
so that's why I...
You believed in us.
Huh?
You believed that we would go save you, right?
That's why you came to get us.
Yeah.
That pin--
It's the Ninja Hero: Edge Shot, right?
Yup!
Do you want to be a hero, too, Katsuma?
My Quirk isn't good for being a hero...
Besides... Mahoro says it's dangerous...
You're part of that famous
U.A.'s hero course, but you're useless.
I see, it's not that Mahoro hates heroes,
it's that she's worried about Katsuma.
Izuku, I can't take this anymore.
You keep getting hurt.
My heart can't take it...
Hey, Katsuma.
What kind of hero do you want to be?
I want to be a strong hero
who can beat up evil villains.
Really? I want to be a hero
who can save people in trouble.
Save people in trouble...?
Yeah.
You want to be a hero who can
defeat the enemy to save people.
I want to defeat the enemy,
so I can save people.
The order is different,
but what we're aiming for is the same--
I think we both want to be the greatest hero.
That's why...
...let's both do our best.
Yeah.
Oh, but we should try not
to worry our families too much.
Yeah!
Little Katsuma really loves heroes, doesn't he?
Here, take this.
Thank you very much, Mrs. Suzumura.
Please be kind to him.
He lost his mother when he was very young.
His father works away from home all year,
so he and his older sister,
Mahoro, live on their own.
Of course, those of us in
the neighborhood look after them.
But it's lonely to not have
parents around at that age.
Mahoro!
Where did you go, Katsuma?
To see Mister Deku.
I went to say sorry for
what happened yesterday.
Why?
I love Daddy.
I want to be someone as cool as Daddy.
But...
But--
Wh-What is it?!
The breakwater...
Why's the ferry coming this way...?
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
What... What's going on?
Chimera, Mummy,
I don't want to be interrupted.
You two are in charge of diversions.
How should we do it?
However you want.
Roger.
Slice.
I know.
V-Villains...
Those are definitely villains.
Mahoro, tell the heroes!
But they're still students...
Mister Deku would help us!
I'm sure of it!
I finished working the fields.
Welcome back, Midoriya.
Good work!
What? If it's a lame job--
Villains appeared at the fishing harbor!
That voice...
You're that damn kid
from yesterday, aren't you?
--Don't think you can keep tricking us--
--I'm not lying!
--I'm telling the truth, Bakugo!
--Hello? It's Deku!
--Bastard.
--At the fishing harbor, vi--
What did Mahoro say?
"Nabu island"
"Base Transceiver Station"
Communications have been cut off.
Next...
I hope she was worried over nothing...
Anyway, I'll go to the fishing harbor.
Thank you so, so much!
Isn't it great, Maakun?
Yeah, Miitan.
What the heck? She had a boyfriend!
Damn that Ashido...
What was that?!
Heroes, it's a v-villain!
It's seriously a villain!
That's too sudden!
W-We need to do something!
Aoyama, use your bellybutton beam!
It's called "Navel Laser"!
Oh? Three heroes in the middle of nowhere?
He just made more...!
Hagakure, did you contact the office?
I can't reach them!
I don't have any signal!
"No Service"
No way!
If I keep shooting, my stomach will...
Damn it!
What should we do?!
Froppy, Tentacole!
Evacuating everyone is our first priority!
Got it!
Get away from here, quickly.
Twirling Tail Dance!
What are you after?
Why are you doing this?!
You're young for a hero.
--Tokoyami!
--Sorry I'm late!
Dark Shadow!
Got it!
We can't use our smartphones.
Go back to the office and get help!
But--
I'll hold things here!
Huh? My phone has no signal!
You're right.
--Mine, too.
--And mine.
What's going on?
Don't tell me...
This is bad! Th-There's a villain!
A villain?!
He's going wild at the shopping arcade!
There are heroes fighting him, but--
Reporting in!
A villain has appeared at the beach!
--What?!
--Ojiro and the others are fighting a defensive battle.
They're asking for help!
--Iida!
--There's no time to hesitate.
Everyone here, split up into two groups
and deal with the villains!
Bakugo, Kirishima, and Kaminari,
intercept the villain at the shopping arcade!
Yaoyorozu, Jiro, and Ashido,
work on relief and evacuation of
the islanders in the shopping arcade!
Todoroki, Sato, Sero, and Tokoyami,
come with me to the beach!
Uraraka and Koda,
you're on relief and evacuation
of the people at the beach!
We're in a race against time.
We're the only heroes on this island.
And we're the only ones who
can save the people on this island!
U.A. High School hero course
Class 1-A, heading out!
The fishing harbor!
I need to tell everyone...
No signal...?
Villains have come to this island.
The others are probably also aware of
the situation and are dealing with them.
Then right now,
I should confirm Mahoro's safety.
Mahoro lives...
...those of us in the
neighborhood look after them.
...near Mrs. Suzumura!
M-My stomach is at its limit...
My scalp is at its limit, too...
Mineta! Aoyama!
You're struggling too much against small fry,
you extras!
Bakugo!
Hey!
Red Riot is on the scene!
Chargebolt is also on the scene!
You two!
Friends, huh?
Everyone!
Yao-momo, everyone!
We'll evacuate the people of
the island and provide first-aid relief.
Right!
Armor-Piercing Shot: Auto-Cannon!
Oh, no!
Sorry!
Bakugo!
Damn it!
What the hell?!
Objects wrapped in my bandages
will move according to my will.
It does not work on living things,
but the materials you have on your body...
Your armor and clothes are all mine to control.
Bakugo!
Fight amongst yourselves!
Ojiro!
Octoblow!
With that appearance,
you must've been bullied a lot.
Did you ever resent your parents for it?!
Huh?
--Shoji!
--Leave this place to us!
Take care of Ojiro!
--Now!
--Tokoyami, Sato!
Sugar Rush!
Don't push your luck!
Sato!
Hey, hey,
even if you're all kids,
there are too many heroes here.
Mahoro, we need to tell
the heroes about the villains!
My cell phone doesn't work,
so I can't do anything about that.
Let's go home first and
let the people in the village--
Our house...
Found you.
Cell activation of type B blood...
Boy, I'm going to steal your Quirk.
Don't worry, I won't kill you.
D-Don't come any closer!
I... I-I said don't come closer!
I know it's just an illusion.
Mahoro...
--Mister Deku!
--Deku!
A super power Quirk...
--Are you okay? Can you run?
--Yeah.
Hurry up and get away from here.
Okay!
Stop!
Why are you targeting those kids?!
Move.
No way I'm moving.
If you're going to get
in the way, then I'll kill you.
An invisible wall?!
A wall made of air?
He fired from his nails?
Two Quirks that aren't related at all...
That's almost exactly like...
...All For One...
Stop, Bakugo!
He's being completely controlled...
What should we do, Kirishima?
You're asking me?
Shoot!
Damn it...
Choose.
Become my puppets...
...or be defeated by your friend...
Stop screwing around!
What?!
Don't underestimate me, mummy bastard!
He sacrificed it on his own...
I stocked up a lot, you know.
Maximum blast...
Die...!
Yeah, good job, Bakugo!
He kept the damage to
the buildings to a minimum, too.
--Everyone!
--Where's the villain?
What? I beat him easily.
What about the islanders?
We've evacuated them all
to the west district.
Where are you going, Bakugo?!
I'll leave the rescuing to you guys!
I'm gonna go crush the other villains!
Damn it, he's holding us down with power.
Iida, what can we do?
Right now, we should only think
about how we can hold this guy here
until the islanders finish evacuating.
Black Abyss!
Reciproburst!
Not putting up much of a fight, heroes!
Wh--?!
At this rate...
Delaware Smash...
...Air Force!
Stone-like blasts of air...
That's an interesting way of using it.
I can't let that guy get close
to Katsuma and Mahoro.
I'll continue to keep him in check like this...
This time it was a gust of wind!
Just how many Quirks does he have?
If the opponent is an unknown, then rather
than take the wait-and-see approach,
I should attack first.
One For All: Full Cowling... 20%!
His power increased...!
With the most power I can use right now...
St. Louis Smash!
Twenty percent... isn't enough?!
This power... this Quirk...
...is worth stealing...
S-Steal? He said "steal"...
He has the same
Quirk as All For One after all...
One For All will be stolen...!
I can't steal it.
No, I don't have enough
free spaces to steal them all...
This kid has the potential
to have more than one Quirk...
Move, body! Move, move!
His very existence is a threat.
Then, I will simply eliminate him...
I was pushed back by a wall of air?
Mister Deku...?
--Mister Deku!
--Deku!
R-Run away...
But...
It's fine, just hurry!
He's after... you tw--
Mister Deku!
Hurry...
Go...!
No... No...
No...!
What is that?
Deku...?
Someone, please...
Protect Deku...!
An exploding Quirk...
Found you, damn villain!
Kacchan!
That's...
Bakugo?!
Kids, look closely!
At the strength of the man who'll become...
...the number one hero!
Got you!
Kacchan!
D-Damn it...
Kacchan, the villain has multiple Quirks.
He steals them!
Damn, like All For One, huh?
Then I've got even more reason to crush him!
If I've seen it once...
...it's not gonna work on me again!
It's got my ribs...!
Move...
Move...!
You just won't stop barking.
The same goes for you!
Damn Deku!
Detroit...
...Sma--
Wh-What's happening...?!
What is that?
The electricity...
Now...
I won't... let you go...
Th-The fight... isn't over yet...
Mister Deku...!
Bakugo!
Heroes really are...
I-Is he in pain?
Why?
Nine!
Get a hold of yourself, Nine.
Th-The boy...
I understand.
Don't struggle.
Don't worry, we're friends.
Now, while they're distracted!
--Tsu!
--Ribbit!
Follow them!
Get that boy no matter what it takes!
Nine,
they can't leave this island.
You should let your body heal right now.
That's it?
You barely escaped with your lives, huh, kids?
He's running away?
It's probably more accurate
to say he's letting us go.
--Damn it.
--Don't go!
It might be a trap.
He's someone we couldn't bring
down even with this many people.
It's dangerous to go after him alone.
But--
We need to check to make sure
the islanders are safe right now.
That's a hero's job, too.
You two are using too much of your Quirks...
We don't know when the villains will be back.
If I don't work too hard here,
then when will I--yay!
You're already in your "yay" mode.
--Here you go.
--Thanks.
It's hot, so be careful.
Please take only one per person!
There's enough for everyone.
What happened to the villains?
Please do not worry.
We will definitely protect you all.
It's a good thing this island
has a lot of ingredients.
What happened to the villain we caught?
Oh, he's been locked up in
the boiler room in the basement.
Apparently, he's not saying anything
no matter how much he's interrogated.
Todoroki, how are Deku and Bakugo?
They haven't regained consciousness yet.
The doctor from the clinic
is treating them, but...
Thank you for your hard work.
Sorry, all our Quirks can do
is to close up their wounds.
We can't do anything about their broken bones.
They'd have to be taken to a hospital
on the main island for more than this.
Let me help.
Katsuma?
Katsuma's Quirk looks like
it's the activation of cells.
We don't know if he can heal
their injuries or not, though...
They got hurt protecting us.
That's why...
I'd like to ask for
your help, too, Little Katsu.
Okay!
I need to save them!
No, I will save them!
How's Nine doing?
He's fine.
He should wake up in a few hours.
Where's Mummy?
He's not here?
Don't tell me the heroes got him?!
Of course not.
Even if that was the case,
our plan will still continue.
It definitely... definitely will.
Why are you saving me?
Come with me.
We will destroy the society where
you were called a monster and a villain.
A world where only the powerful rule...
That's what we'll make.
Join the League of Villains?
Strictly speaking,
I will donate my body to the
League's Quirk-enhancing experiment.
Are you planning on using them?
It's too dangerous.
We need an even greater power.
We bet everything on you.
Don't die on us...
You're compatible with
All For One's Quirk factor.
You've become a being who can
steal eight Quirks and use nine.
The experiment was a success.
With this, our plan is--
But the side effects have also gotten worse.
If I use the Quirks too much,
my body's cellular tissues get destroyed.
That's...
Then there was no point in getting the surgery!
I'll steal a cell activation Quirk.
And then...
...the world we desire...
Katsuma, you should sleep a little...
No, I can keep going.
--But...
--I can do it.
I'm not gonna give up.
A hero doesn't give up...!
Mister Deku!
Bakugo!
First, here's a report on the current situation.
The communications and
electricity grids have been destroyed
and we cannot call for help...
Earlier, I created a drone that
could transmit an S.0.S. message
and sent it toward the main island.
It will take at least six hours to land there.
And then it will take even
more time for help to arrive.
I don't think the villains
will wait that long...
Right now, our highest priority must be
to protect the people of the island...
--How?
--The villain was able to beat up Midoriya and Bakugo so much that they passed out!
The one we fought was also extremely skilled.
Even if we're going to fight,
Yao-momo and Kaminari have both
used up a lot of their Quirks already...
Yay.
Of just the ones we know of,
there are still three villains left.
If they all attack at once,
we won't stand a chance.
At least, if we knew
what the villains were after...
Yeah, then we could come up with a plan.
I'm going to steal your Quirk.
Katsuma--
The villains are after me.
What did you say?
He said that he would steal my Quirk.
Quirk hijacking?
It's just like All For One, huh?
But we know what the villains are after.
We can just take this boy and run away--
It's not going to be that easy.
We're up against villains here.
They could threaten to kill the islanders
if we don't give them the boy.
Then what should we do...?
Give me to the villains!
--What?
--He said he wouldn't kill me.
It's fine if I lose my Quirk.
If that will save everyone on the island...
We can't do that!
Deku?
Midoriya, are you okay now?
Thanks to Katsuma's Quirk.
My Quirk isn't good for being a hero...
Cell activation...
Accelerated cell regeneration...
And even enhanced performance...
Thanks to that,
I've already recovered this much!
It's an amazing Quirk, Katsuma.
Thanks.
Mister Deku...
We won't let anything scary happen to you.
That's what we're here for!
So, we just have to kill
those damn villains, right?
Bakugo!
Save people to win and win to save people.
If you both recognize each other
and can focus on making each other stronger...
...then you can become the greatest heroes.
We will definitely protect you two.
We'll crush those villains.
We'll also definitely
save the people of the island!
We'll definitely win!
Bakugo, Midoriya, I'm on board, too.
I want to protect the people of the island, too.
Let's fight!
If you insist.
If I don't fix the tractor at
Mr. Matsuda's, I'll be stuck at yay.
Me, too. I want Granny Sato to live a long life.
Count me in, too!
And me.
--Me, too.
--Of course!
--Me, too!
--Yeah.
--Ribbit!
All right, let's do this!
Yeah, let's do it.
That's all we can do.
Because we're heroes!
We'll overcome the impossible.
It's something we always say, right?
Go beyond!
Plus Ultra!
Midoriya, what's the plan?
We know there are at least
three villains still out there.
We'll use the castle ruins with
a sheer cliff behind us as our base
and leave the enemy only
a single route to reach us.
Then, split up the villains
with a preemptive strike.
Using the terrain in each area...
...we'll beat them into the ground!
We'll have the people of the island
evacuate into a cave in the cliff.
Katsuma and Mahoro will be guarded by us.
We also should secure an escape route
to use if it comes down to it.
How will we deal with
the one with multiple Quirks?
When Kacchan and I fought him,
he suddenly looked like he was in pain.
It's probably too hard on his body
for him to use the Quirks a lot.
That's why he's trying to steal
Katsuma's cell activation Quirk.
I see, so we'll exhaust him.
We'll attack the villain in waves
and make him use his Quirks.
Since he can steal Quirks,
we'll do this in a way
that avoids close combat if possible.
If that lets us defeat
the villain, that's great.
But even if we can't,
if we can just last until help comes...
...then we can protect everyone.
No.
We'll definitely win.
Nine.
The target is at the top of the castle mountain.
The heroes are, too.
What, a siege?
Let's head toward our goal.
One who will become king
doesn't need to rely on cheap tricks.
They're here. Three of them.
They're walking together
on the route we predicted.
We're counting on you, Yaoyorozu, Aoyama.
Twenty seconds until
the villains reach the spot...
Aoyama, Navel Laser at max output!
Energy charge...!
Five, four, three, two, one!
Can't Stop Twinkling...
...Supernova!
Plus Ultra!
They've split up!
Using the last of my lipids, I made these!
My final attack!
Where are they aimin--
What?!
Phase one, finished...
S-Some leaked out...
We've succeeded in splitting them up!
All right!
The villains are being
lured to the arranged spots!
So far, everything's going according to plan.
We will definitely protect everyone!
Tape Shot...
...Trident!
Release!
Uraraka!
That was close!
Sero!
Make the villain...
...use his Quirks!
Shoot away!
They split us up, huh?
I messed up!
That was close!
Ashido, leave the rest to me.
This is my world.
Cheeky boy.
Damn... They split us up discreetly, huh?
--All right!
--All according to plan.
No.
Hey, that was cold.
We meet again.
Stop that.
Today...
...I'm serious.
We're different today, too!
Now that all the islanders
are evacuated, we can go all out...
...to stop you.
Recipro Turbo!
Let's end this in ten minutes!
--Yeah! --Right!
--Ribbit!
Just what I wanted.
Damn it, we couldn't even slow him down!
What about this?
It's almost time for our real attack!
--Y-Yeah!
--Sero! Uraraka!
Mineta!
I'm ready!
We're counting on you, Uraraka!
Plus...
...Ultra!
Go, Mineta!
Super Grape Rush!
Take that, and that,
and that, and that, and that!
And that, and that,
This was our real attack!
--All right!
--W-We did it...
Are you all right?!
Serves you right...
We've sealed you away...
He defended against the real attack!
The villain's approaching
Uraraka and the others!
In that case...
Aoyama!
Yao-momo!
While you have the chance...
Prepare yourselves--
It's no use.
Playtime's over.
You were still alive?
If you're gonna sleep-talk, then sleep and die!
Bakugo's joined the battle!
--Midoriya?
--Take care of Katsuma and Mahoro!
--Mister Deku!
--Deku!
We'll defend this place till the end!
Take this!
If I can't protect them here,
then there's no point in trying to be a hero!
St. Louis Smash!
It doesn't have to be at full power.
Just think about how
to make him use his Quirks!
X-Catapult!
Not bad...
After this...
...we'll kill you!
What do you mean, "This is my world"?
Say something more energetic!
Is that all you've got?
She's made more moves.
I just need an opening for an instant!
How pathetic.
Black Abyss: Sabbath!
--Now!
--Acid Shot!
We'll decide this all at once!
How dare you...
Ashido!
You little...!
Th... This is...
I won't let you get in Nine's way!
Tokoyami?
Dark Shadow...
Pay attention to what's in front of you!
I know!
It's no use!
Red Gauntlet!
That itches.
I told you brats that it was no use!
M-My body's...?!
There was a reason why we
repeated the same boring moves.
On my legs and Kirishima's hands,
we smeared a toxic mucus made by Asui.
You mean, "Tsu."
Resign yourself, old man!
Acting so insolent...
I'll show you...
...why I'm called a monster!
He's gotten bigger?!
That form makes him look like Amajiki!
--Damn!
--Asui!
Ribbit!
That's where lida and the others are...
Are they having a hard time?
We should go--
You can't!
Our job is to protect Katsuma and Mahoro.
Mister Deku...
Bakugo...
I won't let you!
Sero!
I'll touch him and make him float!
Uraraka!
Not... yet...
Bastard...
How could you?!
We're getting pushed back.
At this rate, Katsuma and Mahoro...
Damn it...
Th-This is...
There it is! His time limit!
That's some crazy power!
We can't even get close to him.
My Recipro will be done soon.
Make an opening for me.
Get me close to him.
And then?
I have an idea.
All right.
This will be our last attack!
Iida, distract him with your Recipro Turbo!
Doesn't this remind you of Camino?
Yeah.
Whatever attack comes,
I'll take it and get you close to him for sure!
Yeah!
Unbreakable!
Kirishima!
Go...
Increase the temperature in
your body to its maximum limit.
What I could do with my flames...
...I'll do with my ice now!
Todoroki!
Go down, as low as possible!
Ribbit!
Freeze!
Hibernate for a while...
W-We've... done... our duty...
Midoriya... Bakugo...
Kacchan, let's attack in waves!
Don't give me orders!
I-If only I could get
the cell activation Quirk...
Let's get a sure hit in here!
...then I wouldn't have to conserve anything!
Mister Deku...
Bakugo...
--Mister Deku!
--Bakugo!
Activation of cells?
Yes.
But I can only activate
the cells of type A blood.
It's not a Quirk that can really help anyone...
Mr. Shimano, do you have any family?
I'm from Nabu Island,
and my daughter and son still live there...
That's pretty far,
but Nabu Island is within
the culprit's range of progression.
"Nabu Island"
but Nabu Island is within
the culprit's range of progression.
"Nabu Island"
Excuse me.
What is it?
A fishing boat sailing near
Kyushu received an S.0.S. message.
Villains have attacked Nabu Island,
and they request help immediately.
That's the suspect in the Quirk-loss crimes!
--What did you say?
--Send a rescue team to Nabu Island immediately!
Oh, and contact U.A. High School.
U.A.? Why?
For the practical hero work recommendation
project sponsored by the commission,
the ones stationed at Nabu Island are
U.A. High School's hero course Class 1-A.
Shoji, take Katsuma and Mahoro
and get out of here.
Please.
All right!
We'll definitely hold him back.
Yeah.
Found you...
Heartbeat Distortion!
Twirling Tail Dance!
Ojiro!
I need to get to the escape route...
G-Get away...!
Run!
Both of you, run!
Hurry!
Go!
Katsuma, run away!
M-Mahoro?
It's fine, just run away!
Don't come any closer!
Don't lay a hand on my little brother!
I said, don't come any closer!
Mahoro!
I-If you don't want her to die,
then come here.
No, run away...
Run away!
Help me...
...turn my desire into reality...
Run... away...
Katsuma...
No!
I will protect you!
I will protect you, Mahoro!
Smash!
Sorry I'm late!
Mister Deku...
You did a good job, Katsuma.
You were amazing!
Bakugo... You're alive...
I told you, didn't I?
I'm the man who'll be even better than All Might
and become the number one hero.
Run away with Mahoro!
Okay!
Mahoro!
How did you avoid my lightning...?!
You used that on us already!
That's why
we used a useless idiot as a lightning rod.
I-Isn't that a bit much?
Smash!
Die!
Over here!
Th...
This can't end!
It can't be the end!
Like I'd let it end like this!
A tornado!
Damn, he really can change the weather...
What should we do?
Katsuma and Mahoro are still here...
On top of that, everyone who's
evacuated could be in danger, too!
Is he planning on destroying this whole island?
We definitely have to stop him!
One For All...
...100%!
I'll blow that away with everything I've got!
Detroit...
...Smash!
Howitzer...
...Impact!
Mister Deku!
Mahoro!
The entrance!
--Sato!
--I can hold this. Get everyone further inside!
E-Even at 100%... it wasn't enough...
D-Damn it...
Even though I lowered myself to fight with Deku...
It's no use.
You will not be able to live
with that level of power.
Not in the new world I will create.
New world...?
Those who have power--
The strong will rule
over the weak in my utopia.
That crap...
It won't matter if someone
is a villain or a hero.
Everything is equal before power...
That...
...is what a true superhuman society should be.
With such a selfish assumption...
You're crazy...!
Are you getting in the way of the new world?
Then you should just disappear.
Think...
What would All Might do...?!
L-Like I'd let it end here!
Think... Think...
I don't want to lose!
Think...
Mister Deku!
Bakugo!
Don't lose!
So that's where you were.
Kacchan...
There's just one way...
There's just one way we can do this...!
My Quirk was passed
on to me like a sacred torch.
The power to transfer power...
K-Kacchan...
A hero has a lot to protect.
That's why I won't lose!
Deku...
A hero...
...can always break out of a tough spot!
A way we can protect...
A way we can win...
There's just one way...
What...?
If you do this,
will you still be able to use it?
I don't know...
But...
All Might still protected us with
the embers after he transferred it to me.
What did you do?!
With two... One For Alls...
...we'll save everyone!
...we'll win!
You two should already be dead...!
This is the end for your dream then, too, huh?
It's fine. This is the only way.
Besides, I'm sure All Might
would say that it's fine if it's you.
If it's you, who shared our secret...
...who admired the same person as me...
If it's you...
All Might really is cool, isn't he?
He's such a cool hero...
No matter what crisis is
in front of him, in the end...
...he always wins!
No matter what trouble they're in, he always...
...saves everyone with a smile!
Don't make me laugh!
Detroit...
...Smash!
Wh-What is this...?
What is that power...?
Don't block...
...my path!
Kacchan, let's go!
Huh?
Don't give me orders!
Don't get in my way!
This is...
...the last...
...that I'll produce...
The last...
...Smash!
Goodbye...
...One For All...
Thank you...
Are you alive, Tokoyami?
Hawks... Why...?
We came first to save you guys...
Me, and one other guy.
A-All Might...
Young Midoriya, sorry I'm late...
Wh-What about Kacchan...?
You always worry about other people first...
He's beat up, but he's fine.
He'll live.
I'm glad...
I made him do something crazy...
Young Bakugo?
All Might...
I-1 transferred it...
One For All... to Kacchan...
One For All?!
If we didn't use two One For Alls,
then we couldn't save
the people of the island...
We couldn't have defeated the villain...
That's why... I don't regret it...
But, I'm sorry...
Even though you chose me
as your successor...
Even though you said I could become a hero...
But I wanted to protect
everyone no matter what...!
Young Midoriya...
I'm sorry, All Might...
I'm sorry...
But I...
Young Midoriya, I don't regret
giving you One For All one bit...
You used it correctly...
The hearts of the brave
that have been spun together...
The power that is the crystallization of that...
One For All...
Before the transfer finished,
because Young Bakugo lost consciousness...
No, that's not it.
For the one who risked his life to protect
and the one who risked his life to win...
...One For All gave them a miracle...
Master... All the predecessors...
Thank you very much...
What are you planning...
...Tomura Shigaraki?
You were alive, as I thought.
Shigaraki...
Did you have a good life?
It's only begun... It's only...
Don't worry. I'll take over your dream.
There only needs to be one ruler...
That's right... only one...
Good night, Nine...
Good work.
Ow...!
What the hell happened?!
Kiss...!
"Undergoing Treatment"
Kacchan doesn't remember anything
about the transfer of One For All,
and even now, One For All lives inside me.
"Nabu Port Terminal"
Daddy!
Mahoro! Katsuma!
Later, Katsuma and Mahoro were
able to reunite with their father.
For this incident, we were able
to protect everyone on the island,
but there was a lot of damage.
The Heroes Public Safety Commission
immediately suspended the program,
but we stayed on the island
until we were scheduled to leave
to help with recovery efforts.
And then, the last day
of the program arrived...
Shouldn't we say something before we leave?
Right?
We shouldn't get in the way of their rebuilding.
Well, I guess leaving without a word...
...is also pretty hero-like.
Yes.
It's time to say goodbye to this island, huh?
Good riddance.
You don't need to say bye to those kids?
There are things I wanted to tell them,
but it's fine...
I'm sure they already know what they are.
Hey!
Mister Deku!
Bakugo!
Everyone!
Thanks for protecting everyone...
...on the island!
Mister Deku, I'll get stronger!
Strong enough to protect Daddy and Mahoro!
And then, I'll become
a cool hero like you and Bakugo!
Don't forget that, damn kid.
Katsuma!
You...
You can become a hero!
I'll be waiting for you at U.A.!
Come, the time for beginnings is at hand
It's goodbye to those tear-filled nights
One banner for the world
that's raised My Gloria anew
Start walking and,
in time, a wind will surely arise
Banner aflutter, let's advance
Come, it's nice to meet you
This story that's awakened
No more hesitation
Start walking
This story of a dawning
Even farther beyond
Walking blind and dazzled
The countless banners at
the end of a headlong plunge
Not a single one like another
Yet each a banner raised with pride
Neither ingratiating nor playful
We're simply travelers going to the same place
Hey, start building
This glory we fell in love with
Let us go together
Walking side by side, in accord, to this parade
Even farther beyond
Though morning may birth shadows
And hope may grow ill
Just keep your faith in the here and now
In the resolve that shines in each of us
March for our cause
Hey, start building
This story of freedom
No more hesitation
Be wrong with one another
to this parade of the dawning
Let us go together
'Til the day the world ends
Let us keep raising the banner
Light up one another, transcending even destiny
Even farther beyond
Us to the beyond
All the way beyond